Passion never dies.
Wicker Park is a drama, mystery, romance film directed by Paul McGuigan.
Matthew, a young advertising executive in Chicago, puts his life and a business trip to China on hold when he thinks he sees
Lisa, the love of his life who left him without a word two years earlier, walking out of a restaurant one day.
Matthew, played by Josh Hartnett.
Alex, played by Rose Byrne.
Luke, played by Matthew Lillard.
Lisa, played by Diane Kruger.
Daniel, played by Christopher Cousins.
Rebecca, played by Jessica Paré.
Wicker Park is a 2004 American romantic thriller drama film directed by Paul McGuigan
and starring Josh Hartnett, Rose Byrne, Diane Kruger and Matthew Lillard.
It is a remake of the 1996 French film L'Appartement, which in turn is
loosely based on Shakespeare's A Midsummer Night's Dream.
It was nominated for the Grand Prix at the Montreal World Film
Festival, the city in which the film was partially filmed.
The title refers to the Wicker Park neighborhood
on Chicago's near northwest side.
The film received generally negative reviews from
critics, and was a box-office disappointment.
The film explores themes of love of one's life, leave, look-alike, intrigue.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.